GEOVANNI MENA

Full-Stack Developer & Web Designer

+593 0993189641

(7) /Geovamena

k geovannimena.com

PROFILE

Ecuadorian promoter based in Quito. Using the latest technologies available, I am willing to grow and challenge myself in environments where I can learn and continue to create amazing dynamic experiences that live on the Internet. My main intention is to know and adapt to the difficulties of the company to solve the work as quickly and efficiently as possible.

I would love to be part of your wonderful team!

EDUCATION

Universidad San Francisco de Quito 🔗

Software Engineering

2020 - 2024

Academio 🤌

Full-Stack Web developer.

01/2022 - 11/2022

SKILLS

TECHNICAL SKILLS (• HTML • CSS • JavaScript/TypeScript • React JS • GitHub • Pvthon • Node JS • MvSOL)

SOFT SKILLS (• Leadership • Problem-solving • Public Speaker • Resourcefulness • Willing to help • Willing to learn new things)

M COURSES

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures. *⊘*

CodeCamp

Scientific Computing with Python *OcioeCamp*

3 LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native), **English** (Intermediate), **Italiano** (Intermediate)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ACADEMLO 8

F-COMMFRCF

08/2022 - 09/2022

For the elaboration of this project, we use **JavaScript** knowledge that we acquired in past projects implementing **React**, **Redux**, **CSS**, Sass for the Front-End.

We also add a login for user registration, purchases and cart to provide the details and the total amount to pay.

POKEDEX

08/2022 - 09/2022

We use the official **API** of a television series called Pokemon, implement **JavaScript** knowledge for the use of **React**, **Redux** and **CSS**. Which we implement an entry to search for the desired pokémon and then click on the card that will give you the details of each Pokemon.

App Rick and Morty

06/2022 - 07/2022

We use the official **API** of a TV series called Rick and Morty, implement **JavaScript** knowledge for the use of **React** to then make the call to APIs and filter on a card the chapter you have pointed out in the browser above.

Weather App

05/2022 - 06/2022

Weather App is my first project implementing the **React** library which we use the official climate **API** called **OpenWeather**, to later make the corresponding call of the degrees centigrade and Fahrenheit of each user's location.

E-COMMERCE

06/2022 - 07/2022

For the construction of this project, we use technologies such as **HTML**, **CSS** and **JavaScript** to give it a logic and perfect performance, we also use Bootstrap to give a better design to the cards.